Let's take a look at an experiment that tracks multiple metrics.
我们来看一个关于跟踪多重指标的实验
And suppose that Audacity sometimes prompts students when they miss quizzes,
假定 Audacity 在学生错过小测试时 鼓励学生
asking if they'd like to contact a coach.
问他们是否愿意和学习教练联系
And they run an experiment that makes this message appear more frequently.
他们做试验使这个信息更频繁地出现
There are a few different metrics they could track here.
这里有几个他们可以追踪的不同的指标
First, they might track the probability that a student signs up for
首先 他们可以追踪
coaching at any point during the course.
学生在课程中选择教练的概率
Second, they might track how early in the course students sign up for
其次 可以追踪学生在课程中
coaching.
选择教练的速度多快
So something like the average amount of progress a student makes before
诸如学生在参与辅导之前
enrolling for coaching.
进步的平均水平
If a student never signs up for coaching, their progress might be 100%.
如果一个学生没有选择辅导 他们的进步可能是 100%
Finally, if coaching is priced differently,
最后 如果辅导的价格是不同的
depending on how early in the course the student signs up,
取决于学生在课上做决定的快慢程度
Audacity might track the average price paid per student.
Audacity 可以追踪学生支付的平均价格
If Audacity tracks all three metrics and
如果 Audacity 追踪三个指标
then does three separate significant tests, with alpha equals 0.05 for each.
然后分别做三个重要的测试 每个测试 α=0.05
Then what is the probability that at least one metric will show
至少有一个指标会显示一个重要差异的可能性是多少？
a significant difference, given that there is no true difference?
假设这里没有正确的差异
In other words, for
换句话说
three metrics, what is the chance of at least one false positive?
三个指标 至少有一个为假正例的概率有多大？
To make the problem easier,
为了使问题简化
I'll first calculate the probability that there are no false positives.
首先计算不出现假正例的概率
That is FP, for false positive, equals 0.
用 FP 表示假正例 FP=0
The chance that each individual metric does not show a false positive is 95%.
每个指标没有出现假正例的概率为 95%
Now in order for none of the metrics to have a false positive, the first one
为了使每个指标都不出现假正例
can't show a false positive, which happens with probability 0.95.
第一个指标不会出现为假正例的概率为 0.95
And neither can the second, so I need to multiply by 0.95.
第二个不会出现的概率也是 0.95 所以需要乘以 0.95
And the third can't have a false positive either, so
第三个也不会出现假正例的概率还是 0.95
I multiply by 0.95 again.
所以再次乘以 0.95
So the chance that none of the metrics shows a false positive is 0.95 cubed,
所以 没有指标出现假正例的概率是 0.95 的立方
which is about 0.857.
大概是 0.857
Then the probability that there is at least one false positive is 1- 0.857.
那么至少出现一个假正例的概率处于 1 到 0.857 之间
Which is a 14.3% chance of any false positive.
是出现任意一个假正例的概率的 14.3%
Now I made an assumption in this calculation.
我在这个计算中做了一个假设
When I multiplied the probabilities together,
当我把这些概率相乘时
I was assuming that the metrics were independent.
我假设指标是独立的
In fact, this isn't true here.
事实上 这并不正确
These three metrics are all related and more likely to move together.
这三个指标是相互联系的 很有可能一起发生变化
So 14.3% is an overestimate of the probability of a false positive.
所以 14.3% 高估了出现假正例的可能性
But assuming independence is an easy way to get a conservative estimate.
但是 假设独立性方便做出保守估计
Now suppose you ran an experiment with ten metrics and
现在 假设你用 10 个指标进行实验
you used a 95% confidence level for each metric.
每个指标的置信度为 95%
Then what would be the probability that any of those
那么 每个指标出现假正例
metrics would show a false positive?
的概率是多少？
Or what if you still had ten metrics but you used a 99% confidence level for
或者 如果你用的指标的置信度为 99%
each metric?
那么每个指标出现假正例的概率是多少?
Write your answers in these boxes.
在这些方框中填入你的答案
Each should be a number between 0 and 1, not a percent chance.
每个应该是 0 到 1 之间的一个数字 不是概率百分比
And you should give each answer to three decimal places.
你给出的每个答案要算到小数点第三位
Assume that the ten metrics are independent of each other.
假设 10 个指标都是彼此独立的